<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CNBC.us">
    <display-name>CNBC</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CNBC.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117010000 +0500" stop="20251117020000 +0500">
    <title>American Greed</title>
    <sub-title>Union Bu$ter; The Fool's Gold</sub-title>
    <desc>Construction workers unwittingly foot the bill for Melissa King's lifestyle; a smooth-talking ladies-man creates a phony gold scheme.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117020000 +0500" stop="20251117030000 +0500">
    <title>American Greed</title>
    <sub-title>Psychic Fiend's Network</sub-title>
    <desc>A phony psychic scams a wealthy but lonely timber baron out of millions while her devious daughter pretends to be in love with him.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117030000 +0500" stop="20251117040000 +0500">
    <title>American Greed</title>
    <sub-title>A Wolf in Priest's Clothing</sub-title>
    <desc>A man concocts a $50 million phony international real estate scheme spending millions on his own lavish lifestyle.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117040000 +0500" stop="20251117050000 +0500">
    <title>American Greed</title>
    <sub-title>A Father's Fraud</sub-title>
    <desc>Karl Karlsen is a hardworking man with what seems to be a terrible streak of bad luck, as his wife and son both die in accidents nearly 20 years apart; Karl has a secret: their suspicious deaths have been keeping his bank account full.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117050000 +0500" stop="20251117060000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>An inventive approach to fish luring; a retail franchise that serves a variety of cereal-centric treats; a product designed to relieve back pain; an update on Bala Bangles.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117060000 +0500" stop="20251117070000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A nutrient-rich energy bar; a gender-neutral clothing brand; a portable children's toy; a healthy Mexican snack company.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117070000 +0500" stop="20251117080000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Brothers from Utah introduce their treasure hunt game experience; entrepreneurs from Wisconsin and New York present their line of streetwear that donates a school uniform to a child in need.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117080000 +0500" stop="20251117090000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Guest shark Kendra Scott; a women's undergarment subscription service; an effortless approach to a classic breakfast meal; an eco-friendly alternative to collecting dog waste; a healthy take on a beloved snack food.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117090000 +0500" stop="20251117100000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A fried food empire; a gardening product; a unique approach to exercise classes; a service that connects customers with local artists.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117100000 +0500" stop="20251117110000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A nutrient-rich energy bar; a gender-neutral clothing brand; a portable children's toy; a healthy Mexican snack company.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117110000 +0500" stop="20251117113000 +0500">
    <title>CNBC Sport: On the Record</title>
    <sub-title>The MVPs</sub-title>
    <desc>Explores the convergence of sports, business, and investing; each week, the biggest names in sports will give an insider's perspective on the strategies, deals, and stories shaping sports and business.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117113000 +0500" stop="20251117120000 +0500">
    <title>CNBC Sport: On the Record</title>
    <sub-title>The Commissioners</sub-title>
    <desc>Conversations with MLB Commissioner Rob Manfred, NCAA President Charlie Baker and NASCAR Commissioner Steve Phelps.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117120000 +0500" stop="20251117123000 +0500">
    <title>America's Next Investment</title>
    <desc>America's Next Investment: Exploring Opportunities in AI,Tech, Real Estate, Alcohol, Cannabis, and More. Tune in to discover how to invest!</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117123000 +0500" stop="20251117130000 +0500">
    <title>NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117130000 +0500" stop="20251117133000 +0500">
    <title>Curry Inc: The Business of Stephen Curry</title>
    <desc>Curry Inc: The Business of Stephen Curry explores how the greatest shooter of all time is preparing for life after basketball. Through exclusive interviews with Stephen Curry, his head coach Steve Kerr, and key executives behind his growing business ventures, CNBC Media &amp; Sports Reporter Alex Sherman takes viewers inside Thirty Ink, Curry's growing business empire.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117133000 +0500" stop="20251117140000 +0500">
    <title>CNBC Sport: On the Record</title>
    <sub-title>The MVPs</sub-title>
    <desc>Explores the convergence of sports, business, and investing; each week, the biggest names in sports will give an insider's perspective on the strategies, deals, and stories shaping sports and business.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117140000 +0500" stop="20251117150000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Squawk Box Europe</title>
    <desc>"Squawk Box Europe" provides three hours of analysis and debate on trading days to lead up to the open of the European markets.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117150000 +0500" stop="20251117160000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Worldwide Exchange</title>
    <desc>Delivering essential, actionable information and analysis for anyone who wants to be part of the global business conversation; preparing CNBC's worldwide audience with a smart take on overnight U.S. news and live international market action.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117160000 +0500" stop="20251117190000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>The big names in business and politics tell their important stories in this pre-market morning news and talk program; from professional traders to casual investors.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117190000 +0500" stop="20251117210000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Taking viewers onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the big companies in the world trade; tick charts track the action of every trade of every stock; the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117210000 +0500" stop="20251117220000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen focus on what is moving the stock markets, the agenda for the business day, detailed data on individual stocks, sectors and the indices that investors and traders want.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117220000 +0500" stop="20251117230000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The front lines of market coverage; host Scott Wapner and the top investors get to the heart of the action as it's happening and help set the agenda for the rest of the day.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251117230000 +0500" stop="20251118000000 +0500">
    <title>Live: The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the important stories to markets and investors; reporters provide actionable information to viewers as they make daily investment decisions.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118000000 +0500" stop="20251118010000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock moving information; delving into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118010000 +0500" stop="20251118020000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Closing Bell</title>
    <desc>A guide through the most important hour of the Wall Street trading day, and taking a close-up look at how the markets are moving, what's driving them and how investors are reacting; coverage includes reports from the CME Group, NASDAQ and the NYSE.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118020000 +0500" stop="20251118030000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Closing Bell: Overtime</title>
    <desc>A look at after-hours moves, including breaking news, corporate earnings and post-market trading; big investors, smart strategists and top money managers debate actionable ideas and the big market themes of the day.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118030000 +0500" stop="20251118040000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Fast Money</title>
    <desc>The information normally reserved for the Wall Street trading floor, enabling viewers to make decisions that give them a chance to make money; the news with an angle that won't be seen until tomorrow's papers.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118040000 +0500" stop="20251118050000 +0500">
    <title>Mad Money</title>
    <desc>Taking viewers inside the mind of one of Wall Street's most respected and successful money managers; Jim Cramer guides viewers through the confusing jungle of Wall Street investing, navigating through both opportunities and pitfalls.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118050000 +0500" stop="20251118060000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A fried food empire; a gardening product; a unique approach to exercise classes; a service that connects customers with local artists.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118060000 +0500" stop="20251118070000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>An entrepreneur returns for a second chance at a deal; an inventor must prove that his creation can turn waste products into gold; a woman wants to expand her handcrafted cookie company.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118070000 +0500" stop="20251118080000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Products include a low-calorie chocolate, a wine to pair with pizza, a medical eye patch for children and an herbal soap for eczema.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118080000 +0500" stop="20251118090000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Pitches include miracle berries, a clothing brand founded on mental health, edible food paint for children and satin-lined headwraps.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118090000 +0500" stop="20251118100000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A convenient new style of eating authentic Korean food; a product designed to help with one's wellness routine; a take on a common cooking tool; a version of a sports medicine product specifically designed for athletes; an update on Souper Cubes.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118100000 +0500" stop="20251118110000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Products include a low-calorie chocolate, a wine to pair with pizza, a medical eye patch for children and an herbal soap for eczema.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>