<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CNBC.us">
    <display-name>CNBC</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CNBC.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118000000 +0500" stop="20251118010000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock moving information; delving into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118010000 +0500" stop="20251118020000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Closing Bell</title>
    <desc>A guide through the most important hour of the Wall Street trading day, and taking a close-up look at how the markets are moving, what's driving them and how investors are reacting; coverage includes reports from the CME Group, NASDAQ and the NYSE.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118020000 +0500" stop="20251118030000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Closing Bell: Overtime</title>
    <desc>A look at after-hours moves, including breaking news, corporate earnings and post-market trading; big investors, smart strategists and top money managers debate actionable ideas and the big market themes of the day.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118030000 +0500" stop="20251118040000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Fast Money</title>
    <desc>The information normally reserved for the Wall Street trading floor, enabling viewers to make decisions that give them a chance to make money; the news with an angle that won't be seen until tomorrow's papers.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118040000 +0500" stop="20251118050000 +0500">
    <title>Mad Money</title>
    <desc>Taking viewers inside the mind of one of Wall Street's most respected and successful money managers; Jim Cramer guides viewers through the confusing jungle of Wall Street investing, navigating through both opportunities and pitfalls.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118050000 +0500" stop="20251118060000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A fried food empire; a gardening product; a unique approach to exercise classes; a service that connects customers with local artists.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118060000 +0500" stop="20251118070000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>An entrepreneur returns for a second chance at a deal; an inventor must prove that his creation can turn waste products into gold; a woman wants to expand her handcrafted cookie company.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118070000 +0500" stop="20251118080000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Products include a low-calorie chocolate, a wine to pair with pizza, a medical eye patch for children and an herbal soap for eczema.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118080000 +0500" stop="20251118090000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Pitches include miracle berries, a clothing brand founded on mental health, edible food paint for children and satin-lined headwraps.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118090000 +0500" stop="20251118100000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>A convenient new style of eating authentic Korean food; a product designed to help with one's wellness routine; a take on a common cooking tool; a version of a sports medicine product specifically designed for athletes; an update on Souper Cubes.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.us" start="20251118100000 +0500" stop="20251118110000 +0500">
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>Products include a low-calorie chocolate, a wine to pair with pizza, a medical eye patch for children and an herbal soap for eczema.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>