<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CNBC.TV.18.in">
    <display-name>CNBC TV 18</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CNBC-TV-18.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117000000 +0500" stop="20251117003000 +0500">
    <title>Converge Live</title>
    <desc>The host presents a detailed report of the latest news stories about business, sports, and entertainment from all around the world, live.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117003000 +0500" stop="20251117010000 +0500">
    <title>On Assignment</title>
    <desc>International correspondents explore compelling global stories through immersive field reporting and personal testimonies from those most affected.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117010000 +0500" stop="20251117020000 +0500">
    <title>Unlocked</title>
    <desc>In order to attain their dream house, people go above and beyond to navigate a tough market and challenging responsibilities.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117020000 +0500" stop="20251117030000 +0500">
    <title>American Greed</title>
    <desc>The host sheds light on some of the biggest white collar crimes committed in the USA and also takes a look at the menace of common financial crimes affecting the average American citizen.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117030000 +0500" stop="20251117060000 +0500">
    <title>Squawk Box Asia</title>
    <desc>The hosts cover Asias business trading day, stock market news and experts views.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117060000 +0500" stop="20251117073000 +0500">
    <title>Street Signs Asia</title>
    <desc>The host provides various updates on daily market-related stories and converses with numerous experts to shed light on their perspectives.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117073000 +0500" stop="20251117083000 +0500">
    <title>Bazaar Morning Call</title>
    <desc>The hosts shed light on the condition of the stock market prior to its opening.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117083000 +0500" stop="20251117093000 +0500">
    <title>Bazaar Open Exchange</title>
    <desc>The host provides the latest news and updates related to the stock markets.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117093000 +0500" stop="20251117100000 +0500">
    <title>Bazaar Corporate Radar</title>
    <desc>The host invites the top businessmen, economists and analysts to provide their perspectives on the latest trends in the market.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117100000 +0500" stop="20251117110000 +0500">
    <title>Capital Connection</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive and detailed coverage of the latest stock market developments, with insights into the latest business news.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNBC.TV.18.in" start="20251117110000 +0500" stop="20251117140000 +0500">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Experts provide pre-market updates that are useful for investors and professional traders and discuss various important developments in the world of stock markets.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>