<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CNN.International.us">
    <display-name>CNN International</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CNN-International.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118000000 +0500" stop="20251118010000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Isa Soares Tonight</title>
    <desc>Isa Soares breaks down the day's news.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118010000 +0500" stop="20251118020000 +0500">
    <title>Live: What We Know With Max Foster</title>
    <desc>Max Foster has a definitive roundup of the day's top stories, giving you the urgent need-to-know context; a deeper dive into the questions sparking debate around the world.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118020000 +0500" stop="20251118024500 +0500">
    <title>Live: Quest Means Business</title>
    <desc>Richard Quest offers a dynamic look at the day's global business stories.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118024500 +0500" stop="20251118030000 +0500">
    <title>Quest's World of Wonder</title>
    <sub-title>Marmaris, Turkey</sub-title>
    <desc>Richard Quest is no stranger to Turkey; this time he is looking at the country from a completely different perspective: as seen from the sea; on board a traditional Turkish gulet, he explores the coastline.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118030000 +0500" stop="20251118033000 +0500">
    <title>Live: The Lead With Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>Covering all the day's top stories around the country and the globe, from politics to money, sports to popular culture.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118033000 +0500" stop="20251118040000 +0500">
    <title>Live: World Sport</title>
    <desc>Up-to-the minute sports news, highlights and analysis plus interviews with the biggest names in global sport.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118040000 +0500" stop="20251118050000 +0500">
    <title>Live: The Brief with Jim Sciutto</title>
    <desc>The best of CNN's reporting from correspondents across the world, to guide global audiences through the fast-paced news cycle with insight, analysis and hard-hitting interviews.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118050000 +0500" stop="20251118060000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett stays ahead of the headlines, delivering a show that's in-depth and informative.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118060000 +0500" stop="20251118070000 +0500">
    <title>Live: Anderson Cooper 360</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper goes beyond the headlines with in-depth reporting and investigations; Anderson keeps his commitment to holding those in power accountable; joining him are guests that frequently include political and legal analysts.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118070000 +0500" stop="20251118080000 +0500">
    <title>Live: The Source With Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>Kaitlan Collins is chasing the facts, asking the tough questions and connecting with her sources.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118080000 +0500" stop="20251118090000 +0500">
    <title>Live: CNN NewsNight With Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>Abby Phillip leads a roundtable discussion on the day's biggest stories and issues shaping our world.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118090000 +0500" stop="20251118100000 +0500">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>Laura Coates goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="CNN.International.us" start="20251118100000 +0500" stop="20251118110000 +0500">
    <title>Live: The Story Is With Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>Elex Michaelson tackles the breaking stories making headlines with sharp analysis, fresh perspective, and a dose of humor.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>