<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Hope-Channel-NZ">
    <display-name>Hope Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Hope-Channel-NZ.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125000000 +0500" stop="20251125003000 +0500">
    <title>Mad About Marriage</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>Neal McCoy, two-time Entertainer of the Year, is one of country music's most beloved entertainers. He's with us today to talk about making fans happy and what makes him happy.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125003000 +0500" stop="20251125010000 +0500">
    <title>Lifestyle Magazine</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>We're going to meet a woman with an unstoppable resolve, who's triumphed over cancer, four times. Join us as we chat with award-winning, film producer Suzanne Lyons.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125010000 +0500" stop="20251125013000 +0500">
    <title>The Evidence</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>Dwight Nelson investigates prayer, and how recent scientific studies demonstrate the power of prayer.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125013000 +0500" stop="20251125020000 +0500">
    <title>Explore</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>Have you ever been fooled by a counterfeit? Explore how the devil has misrepresented the character of God and every truth he has ever given us. The Bible reveals the truth and what God is really like.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125020000 +0500" stop="20251125023000 +0500">
    <title>InVerse</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>At eighty five Caleb claimed the hardest mountain with unshaken faith. Learn how God calls young and old alike to trust His promises and serve boldly at every age.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125023000 +0500" stop="20251125030000 +0500">
    <title>Unhooked</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>The euphoric high of winning is discussed, along with the effect that losing has on financial, emotional and physical health. In her own words, Cindy tells how her gambling grew out of control.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125030000 +0500" stop="20251125033000 +0500">
    <title>Body of Evidence</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>Dr Menton explains that the skin is the largest organ in the body but without the aid of the microscope we cannot appreciate its complexity and many important functions - part 1.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125033000 +0500" stop="20251125040000 +0500">
    <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>Ron Clouzet finds answers to some of the most frequently asked questions about religion, the Bible, and philosophy.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125040000 +0500" stop="20251125043000 +0500">
    <title>Authentic</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>This week on Authentic, discover why God set the seventh day apart and how this forgotten commandment can help us connect with God in a new dimension.</desc>
  </programme><programme channel="Hope-Channel-NZ" start="20251125043000 +0500" stop="20251125053000 +0500">
    <title>Kew Gardens - Season By Season</title>
    <sub-title>Religion</sub-title>
    <desc>The Tree Gang are busy mulching the 14,000 trees that make up the arboretum and Tony is on Cherry Walk to lay out his ambitions for the display.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>